Guide to the Reston Reflections oral history collection, 1994-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 3: 1996 Interviews (Volunteers), 1996, (6 boxes)
  - Loar, Philip, May 12, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    465.13
  - Loux, Ridge, May 8, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    465.14
  - Lyman, Eddy, April 21, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    465.15
  - Maddock, Melinda S., May 14, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    465.16
  - MacIntyre, Pat, May 11, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    465.17
  - Markley, Philip, May 13, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    465.18
  - Martin, Gail, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    465.19
  - Mascia, Vincent Edward, May 15, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    465.20
  - McCarthy, Pia, May 4, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 21)
    465.21
  - McDevitt, Marcia, April 27, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    465.22
  - Miller, David, May 10, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    465.23
  - Miller, Jennifer, May 12, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 24)
    465.24
  - Mills, Betty, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 25)
    465.25
  - Murphy, Jeff, May 21, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 26)
    465.26
  - Nixon, Dorothy, May 21, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 27)
    465.27
  - Novack, Churck, May 14, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 28)
    465.28
  - Nuss, Donald, May 15, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 29)
    465.29
  - Oberreuter, Robert, May 11, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 30)
    465.30
  - Olmes, Pamela, May 21, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 31)
    465.31
  - Ou Yang, Benjamin, May 11, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 32)
    465.32
  - Overton, Ruth, April 8, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 33)
    465.33
  - Payne, Alica, May 20, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 34)
    465.34
  - Peacock, Carolyn, April 20, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 35)
    465.35
  - Pettinger, Connie, May 7, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 36)
    465.36
  - Pierson, Ellen, May 19, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 37)
    465.37
  - Pillai, Nalini, May 5, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 38)
    465.38
  - Presti, Sally, April 26, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    466.1
  - Prince, Jonathan Merl, May 22, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    466.2
  - Rodis, Mike, May 19, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    466.3
  - Rosenbaum, Mary Jane, May 19, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    466.4
  - Robinson, J. David, May 13, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    466.5
  - Robertston, William B., May 9, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    466.6
  - Roland, David, May 15, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    466.7
  - Rosenberg, Charlie, May 11, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    466.8
  - Rosenmund, Bill, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    466.9
  - Salin, Dino, April 24, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    466.10
  - Schrader, Madelyn, May 21, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    466.11
  - Schultz, Elizabeth, May 13, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    466.12
  - Showers, Debbie, May, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    466.13
  - Shwartz, Greg, May 25, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    466.14
  - Siegel, Danny, May 6, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    466.15
  - Silver, Sandy, May 19, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    466.16
  - Simon, Robert (Jr.), 1996 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    466.17
  - Simon, Robert E., June 13, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    466.18
  - Skerrit, Michael, April 24, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    466.19
  - Smith, Jung Lea, April 28, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    466.20
  - Snyder, Sharon Kobal, April 22, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    466.21
  - Sollenberger, Howard, May 11, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 22)
    466.22
  - Spessard, Dianne, May 12, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 23)
    466.23
  - Strange, Ann, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 24)
    466.24
  - Todd, Terlene Terry, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 25)
    466.25
  - Thoesen, Rick, May 14, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 26)
    466.26
  - Thompson, Warren M., May 6, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 27)
    466.27
  - Tillman, Brenda, April 21, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 28)
    466.28
  - Turner, James Michael, May 20, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 29)
    466.29
  - Tripathl, Satish, May 19, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 30)
    466.30
  - Via, Kim, May 29, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 31)
    466.31
  - Warstler, Patricia, May 13, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 32)
    466.32
  - Welch, Lynn, May 18, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 33)
    466.33
  - Welch, Timothy James, May 18, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 34)
    466.34
  - Wills, Jane, April 28, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 35)
    466.35
  - Winger, Cassandra R., May 21, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 36)
    466.36
  - Aguero, Lloyd, April 28, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    467
  - Anselene, Susan, April 27, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Babineau, Diane, May 4, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Benton, Tom, May 19, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Berman, Stephen, May 19, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Bliss, Richard, April 13, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Bollinger, David, April 21, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Bolston, Dan, May 18, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Bouie, Bill, May 15, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Bourn, Deacon, May 12, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Boyd, Margaret, May 13, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Corey, Steven, June 2, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Crutchfield, William (Dr.), May 15, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Decastro, Elizabeth, June 6, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Despins, Monica, May 9, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Dix, Robert, May 6, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Drewes, Jane, May 19, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Eckert, Mary, May 5, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Gerguson, Hal, May 8, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Fink, Dan, April 19, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Foster, Kim, May 12, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Freer, Pam, May 14, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Gatz, Donald, April 17, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Gerdin, Donna, April 27, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Grant, Pamela, May 3, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Greenspan, Laura, May 14, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Rosalind, Gold, April 29, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - Goldberg, Benjamin, May 14, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - Harroun, Sharon, June 14, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - Harroun, Sharon, May 7, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - Harwood, Beverly, May 19, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 31)
  - Holmes, Greg, April 28, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 32)
  - Hickman, James, April 25, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 33)
  - Jackson, Mary, April 24, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 34)
  - Jackson, Mary, April 24, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 35)
  - Jelinek, Pam, May 15, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    468
  - Jones, Suzi, April 27, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Kain, George, May 2, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Kane, Patrick, April 26, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Krebs, Joe, May 17, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Larobardier, Fritz, May 9, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Lena, Vic, May 7, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Lilenthal, Lynn, April 22, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Loar, Phil, May 12, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Loux, Ridge, May 20, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Lyman, Eddy, April 21, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Madock, Melinda, May 14, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Markley, Phil, May 13, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Mascia, Vincent Edward (Dr.), May 15, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - McCarthy, Pia, May 4, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - McDevitt, Marcia, April 27, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Miller, David, May 10, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Miller, Jennifer, May 11, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Murphy, Jeff, May 21, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Nixon, Dorothy, May 13, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Novack, Chuck, May 14, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Nuss, Don, May 15, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Oberreuter, Robert, May 11, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Olmes, Pam, May 14, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Ou Young, Benjamin, May 11, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Overton, Ruth, October 6, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Payne, Alicia, May 15, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Peacock, Carolyn, April 20, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - Pettinger, Constance, May 7, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - Piersou, Ellen, May 19, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - Pillai, Nalini, May 5, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Presti, Sally, April 26, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    469
  - Regen, Andrew, May 12, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Robertson, Bill, May 9, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Robinson, J. David, April 22, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Rodis, Mike, May 19, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Roland, David, May 15, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Rosenbaune, Mary Jane, May 19, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Rosenberg, Charlie, May 11, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Rosenmund, Bill, May 14, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Salin, Dino, April 24, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Schrader, (Mrs.), May 5, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Schultz, Elizabeth, May 13, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Showers, Debbie, May 17, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Swartz, Greg, May 25, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Siegel, Danny, May 6, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Silver, Sandy, May 19, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Simon, Robert, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Simon, Robert E., June 13, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Skerritt, Michael, April 24, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Jung Lea, April 28, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Sollenberger, Howard, May 11, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Thoesen, Rick, May 14, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Thompson, Warren, May 6, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Tillman, Brenda, April 21, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Terry-Todd, (Mrs.), 1996 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Tripathi, Satish, May 19, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Turner, James, May 15, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Vick, Kim, April 29, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - Warstler, Patricia, May 14, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Welch, Tim, May 18, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - Welch, Lynn, May 18, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 31)
  - Wills, Jane (Mrs.), April 28, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 32)
  - Winger, Cassandra, May 11, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 33)
- Series 4: 2001, 2003 and 2009 Interviews (33 boxes), 2001, 2003, 2009; (33 boxes)
  These are additional transcripts and audiotapes completed by the students at Langeston Hughes Middle School. The topics covered are Life Cycle of Neighborhood in 2001 and the War and Community in 2003 among others. They were processed separately but have now been organized with the entire Reston Reflection collection.
  - Alcorn, Kristina, May 2001 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    506D.7
  - Andersen, Kenneth, May 25, 2001 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Anderson, Robert, May 2003 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    506F.1
  - Anderson, Robert, May 2003 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    506G.4
  - Astudillo, Luis, May 2003 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    506G.2
  - Ball, Ruth, April 2003 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Barbiery, Anne, May 2001 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    506D.8
  - Barenz, Shiela, June 14, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Barnum, H.C., May 21, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Barokas, Judy, May 2003 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    506F.4
  - Bauer, Tom, May 2001 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    506E.1
  - Bennett, Arthur, May 2001 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Bennett, William (Capt.), April 2003 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Berlin, Rena, May 2001 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    506E.2
  - Blum, Nancy, May 2001 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    506D.6
  - Bonner, Ken, May 2001 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    506D.5
  - Bouie, William, May 2001 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    506D.4
  - Boyd, Margaret, May 2001 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    506D.3
  - Boyle, Rebecca, May 17, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Braithwait, Gary, May 2003 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Braithwait, Gary and Melissa Kirkpatrick, May 2001 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    506C.1
  - Buck, Eugene H., May 2001 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Burstein, Floye, May 2001 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    506C.2
  - Burton, Greg, May 2001 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    506C.4
  - C.,Mike, May 2001 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Cade, Alfred, May 2003 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    506F.2
  - Conning, Cindy, May 2003 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    506G.1
  - Carroll, Jay, May 2001 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    506C.9
  - Chen, Stephanie, May 22, 2001 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Christian, Prentice, May 2001 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    506C.5
  - Clarridge, Margaret, May 26, 2003 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Cleveland, James, May 2001 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    506C.6
  - Cole, Shauna, May 2001 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    506C.7
  - Collier, Susan, May 2003 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    506.3
  - Contos, Nancy, May 17, 2003 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Courtney, Thomas and Donna, May 2001 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    506C.3
  - Crisler, Tim, May 11, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Cross, Connie, May 2001 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    506D.2
  - D'Alesandro, Thomas, May 2001 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    506D.1
  - Dalton, Laura, May 2001 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    506C.8
  - DeCola, Freya, May 2003 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    506E.4
  - Eurich, Bob, May 2003 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    506F.5
  - Farrell, John D., May 2003 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Farzad, Zohreh, April 2003 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Fatoorechie, Banafsheh B., April 2003 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Fellows, Susan, May 2003 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Fenwick, Mary Kaye, May 2003 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    506E.6
  - Ferrer, Alfred, May 2003 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    506F.7
  - Fisher, Richard, May 2003 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Fitzgerald, Melissa, May 2001 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Gentilella, Kris, May 2001 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Gerstin, Susann, April 2003 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Gibson, Richard, May 2003 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Gibson, Stewart, May 2001 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Gibson, Stuart and Adrienne, May 2003 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    506F.6
  - Glazer, Steve, April 2003 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Gold, Rosalind, May 2001 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Gordon, Leild, May 2001 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Gordon, Leila, May 2001 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Grana, Clare, May 2001 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Graves, Ellen, May 2001 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Greelis, Michael, June 2001 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Greenberg, Wayne (Mr.), May 14, 2003 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Greene, Vicki, May 2001 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Grillo, Ed, May 2001 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Grubisich, Tom, May 2001 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Guilfoyle, John, May 2001 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Guthrie, Michael, May 2001 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Hanrahan, Nancy, May 2001 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Hanson, Margaret, May 2, 2001 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Haring, Jo, May 2001 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Heinz, Howard, June 2, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Henries-King, Andia, April 2003 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Herb, Bob, May 2001 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Herbert, Allen, May 2001 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Herdell, Mary (Mrs.), June 12, 2001 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Hill, Bruce (Mr.), April 2003 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Holly, Joyce, May 2001 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Horton, Lois, May 20, 2001 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Howell, Janet, April 2003 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Howell, Janet, May 14, 2001 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Ingrisono, Erin, May 2001 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Isaacs, Benno, June 11, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Jackson, Deborah, April 2003 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Jackson, Mary, May 2001 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Jackson, Michael, May 11, 2003 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Everett, April 2003 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Jones, Adelie, May 18, 2003 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Kamstra, Thomas, May 17, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Kane, Patrick, May 2001 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Kirkpatrick, Renee, May 2001 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Klein, Suzy, May 2003 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    506E.7
  - Knapp, Kimberly, April 2003 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Krueger, Marjorie, May 2001 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Kudeviz, Debra, May 2003 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    506G.3
  - Kuett, Barbara, May 2001 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Lacy, Duane, May 2001 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Lague, Irene, May 2001 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Lanzane, Dale, May 2001 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Larson, Nancy, April 2003 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Larson, Nancy, May 2001 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - LaRue, Ed, May 17, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - LaRue, Ed, May 2001 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Layson, Bill and Lex (Dr. and Mrs.), April 2003 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Lovaas, Fran, May 2001 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Loux, Ridge, May 2001 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Macdonald, Lydia, June 11, 2001 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Male, Lois, May 2001 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Mapar, Jalal, May 2001 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Mashinski, William A., May 2001 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - McDonnell, June, May 2001 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Mcglocklin, (Mr.), May 2001 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Menard, Millie, April 2003 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Mendenhall, Rhanda, May 2001 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Mennard, Millie, June 2001 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Merrill, Tracey, May 2001 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Meyerick, Brian, May 2001 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Miester, Stephen, April 2003 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Miller, Herbert, May 2001 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Richard, May 2001 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Mitchell, Linda, May 2001 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Moore, Christopher, May 2001 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Morgan, Jim, May 2001 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Munson, William C., April 2003 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Myers, Marion C., May 2001 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Ngamsanith, La, May 2003 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Nicoson, William, May 2001 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - O'Conner, Michael, May 2001 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - O'Gorman, Boofie, May 2001 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Ou Yang, Lin-Min (Mr.), April 2003 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Palka, Robert, May 2003 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Pavek, Bryn, May 2001 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Perlik, Bill, April 2003 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Petrosian, Gregory, May 2001 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Pierce, Christine, May 2003 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Plum, Ken, May 2001 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Pronske, Kurt, May 2003 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    506E.3
  - Raybould, Tom, April 2003 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Reid, Victoria, May 2003 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Riley, Ross, May 2001 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Ritchey, Joe, May 2001 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Robinson, Kathi, May 2001 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Rogers, Kay, May 2003 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Rogers, Thomas T. (Jr.), June 2003 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Romano, Bill and Marsha, May 2001 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Rubin, Betty Ann, May 2001 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Rundlett, Brad (Father), May 2001 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Russell, Laurie, May 2003 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    506F.8
  - Ruszica, Miroslav, May 2003 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Sager, Dennis, May 2001 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Santangelo, Michael, May 2003 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    506G.5
  - Schiffelbein, Wayne, June 2001 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Schram, Sue, April 2003 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Schultz, Betsy, May 2001 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Sherman, Robin, May 2001 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Schreiner, William, April 2003 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Sielski, Edna, May 2001 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Simon, Robert E., May 2001 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Singer, Linda, May 2001 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Sprung, George, April 2003 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Steffan, Jack, May 2003 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Stevenson, Cynthia, April 2003 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Stokes, Eleanore, May 2001 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Swanson, Karen, May 2001 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Taran, Nadia, May 2001 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Teti, Dominick, May 2001 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Theis, Rick, May 2003 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    506E.5
  - Thillman, John, May 2001 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Thomas, Odessa, June 2001 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Tobalske, Bonnie, June 2001 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Toxopeus, Ruth, May 2001 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Turner, Alex, April 2003 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Ungerer, Susan, May 2001 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Vagnozzi, Junita, April 2003 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Veatch, Charles, May 2001 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Vogelson, Susan (Ms.), May 2001 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Volloy, Gerald, April 2003 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Wells, Sally, April 2003 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Werner, Gisela, May 2001 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Wilcox, Dick, May 2003 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Wilde, Sydney Kay, April 2003 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Wingert, Vicky, May 2001 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Wishard, Anne, May 2001 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Yi Oei, Ting, May 2003 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Zablotney, Gene, April 2003 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Zhao, Janet, May 2001 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Albano, Jacqui, June 2009 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Allen, Tara, June 2009 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Alley, Jennifer, June 2009 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Amendola, Roger, June 2009 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Arlington, Caroline, June 2009 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Arrington, Timothy, June 2009 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Badgett, Elizabeth, June 2009 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Bonnes, Bonita, June 2009 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Bauer, Joanne, June 2009 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Arrington, Barbara, June 2009 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Beagan, Bob, June 2009 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Beaver, Barbara, June 2009 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Bensinger, Frank, June 2009 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Mrs. Benson, June 2009 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Bernstein, Simon, June 2009 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Best, Catherine, June 2009 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Beza, Elleke, June 2009 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Bibeault, Daniel, June 2009 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Blackemore, Kristen, June 2009 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Bolton, Vade, June 2009 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Burwell, Earle, June 2009 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Butler, Bruce, June 2009 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Cavalieri, Patricia, June 2009 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Cengiz, Serhat, June 2009 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Christiansen, Richard, June 2009 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Cline, Elizaebth, June 2009 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Smith-Cobbs, Stephen, June 2009 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Cook, Elizabeth Whitham, June 2009 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Cooper, Diane, June 2009 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Curley, Sue, June 2009 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Danaher, Chen, June 2009 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Daniels, Pauline, June 2009 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Dean, John, June 2009 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Dilldine, Debbie, June 2009 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - DiTrapani, Marcia, June 2009 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Dueno, Deana, June 2009 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Elsawg, Claudia, June 2009 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Erickson, Ann, June 2009 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Evans, Charles, June 2009 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Fosper, Rune, June 2009 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Gibson, Stu, June 2009 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Goard, Melane, June 2009 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Gold, Rabbi, June 2009 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Goodson, Wynetta, June 2009 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Gordon, Leila, June 2009 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Groves, Lisa, June 2009 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Gutsick, Joe, June 2009 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Pfeffer-Hahn, Kathie, June 2009 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Handerahan, Leigh, June 2009 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Herron, Kathleen, June 2009 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Hudgins, Cathy M., June 2009 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Hughes, Lisa, June 2009 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Isaacs, Carol, June 2009 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Jenus, Rande, June 2009 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Jewell, Mike and Nancy, June 2009 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Kammerer, Harvey, June 2009 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Kelly, J.S., June 2009 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Kidd, Nancy Alease, June 2009 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Kidwell, Richard and Susie, June 2009 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Klein, Jill, June 2009 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Lu, Lin, June 2009 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Marson, Charlotte, June 2009 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Martin, Maryanne, June 2009 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Mason, Edna, June 2009 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Mattern, Nancy, June 2009 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Mayo, Christine, June 2009 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - McCabe, Susan, June 2009 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - McKee, Michael, June 2009 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - McLerran, Jean, June 2009 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Mennard, Millie, June 2009 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Merrill, Tracy, June 2009 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Minarik, Eileen, June 2009 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Morovitz, Mickie, June 2009 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Moss, Jimmy, June 2009 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Murphy, Haley, June 2009 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Myers, Marion, June 2009 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Neilson, Maleen, June 2009 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Noble, Kathy, June 2009 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Nusbaum, John, June 2009 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - O'Connell, Wendy, June 2009 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Odlen, Janie, June 2009 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Ogg, Betty, June 2009 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - O'Gorman, Mary, June 2009 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Oladimeji, Nonye, June 2009 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - O'Neill, Marilyn, June 2009 (Box 122, Folder 5)